Edwin B. Rollins Papers MS054
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1850 -- 1961; 1930 -- 1955; MS054.003; 0.5 Linear Feet; 565 Digital Object(s)
  - 88 Professors Row, 1954; MS054.003.DO.02144; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - 48 Professors Row, 1876; MS054.003.DO.02145; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Marshall House, 48 Professors Row, 1858; MS054.003.DO.02146; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Marshall House, 1858; MS054.003.DO.02147; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Class of 1876, MS054.003.DO.02178; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts Misc."
    People; Students; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Unidentified man with shovel looking at tree, 1858; MS054.003.DO.02179; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - West end of Professors Row from the Rez, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02180; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts Views"
    Views; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of the old campus, 1871; MS054.003.DO.02181; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Graduating class of 1871, MS054.003.DO.02182; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Tufts crew on the Mystic River, 1874; MS054.003.DO.02184; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Athletics; Crew; People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Crew
  - Ramp leading down to the Tufts railroad station, 1861; MS054.003.DO.02185; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Railroad stations; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View southeast from Ballou Hall, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02186; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View north from Packard Hall, 1875; MS054.003.DO.02187; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - East end of Professors Row, 1875; MS054.003.DO.02188; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of Professors Row from the Rez, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02189; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of the Rez from Ballou Hall, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02191; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Tufts railroad station, 1861; MS054.003.DO.02192; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Football game: Tufts vs. Lafeyette (final score Tufts 7 & Lafeyette 22), 1911 -- 1960; MS054.003.DO.02193; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Views; Athletics; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Football
  - View of the Hill from Stearn's estate, 1875; MS054.003.DO.02194; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of Ballou Hall from East Hall, 1863; MS054.003.DO.02195; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Views; Buildings; Academic; Administrative; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of the Hill from the southeast, 1877; MS054.003.DO.02196; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of President Ballou's home from Ballou Hall, 1860; MS054.003.DO.02197; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Views; Houses; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Old railroad station, 1886; MS054.003.DO.02198; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View southeast from Ballou Hall, 1876; MS054.003.DO.02199; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Old campus from Ballou Hall, 1876; MS054.003.DO.02200; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of Ballou Hall and West Hall from the corner of Professors Row and Packard Avenue, 1877; MS054.003.DO.02201; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Academic; Dormitories; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of Ballou Hall and the chapel tower from West Hall, 1876; MS054.003.DO.02202; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Chapels; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of campus from the Rez, 1886; MS054.003.DO.02203; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View southeast from Ballou Hall, 1873; MS054.003.DO.02204; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of campus from corner of Curtis and Professors Row, 1884; MS054.003.DO.02205; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View south from Ballou Hall, 1876; MS054.003.DO.02206; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View south from Ballou Hall, 1874; MS054.003.DO.02207; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of campus from clay pits off College Avenue in Medford, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02208; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View south from Ballou Hall, 1874; MS054.003.DO.02209; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Professor Gardner C. Anthony, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02210; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts People"
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Anthony, Gardner Chace; College of Engineering
  - Professor George T. Knight, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02211; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Knight, George T.
  - Dr. Thomas Jefferson Sawyer, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02212; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Sawyer, Thomas Jefferson; Board of Trustees
  - Professor Edwin B. Rollins, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02213; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Rollins, Edwin B.; College of Engineering
  - Tufts alumus and lifetime trustee Eugene B. Bowen, 1876; MS054.003.DO.02214; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Alumni and alumnae; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Bowen, Eugene B.; Board of Trustees
  - W.L. Hooker, 1875; MS054.003.DO.02215; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Hooker, W. L.
  - Hosea Ballou, 1858; MS054.003.DO.02216; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; College presidents; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Ballou, Hosea, 2d
  - Professor Charles E. Fay, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02217; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Fay, Charles Ernest; Dept. of Modern Languages
  - Professor Benjamin Franklin Tweed, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02218; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Tweed, Benjamin Franklin
  - Professor Charles D. Bray, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02219; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Bray, Charles Durlin; College of Engineering
  - Professor Frank P. Graves, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02220; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Graves, Frank P.
  - President Elmer H. Capen, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02221; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; College presidents; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Capen, Elmer Hewitt
  - President E.H. Capen, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02222; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Professor Jerome Schneider, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02223; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Schneider, Jerome
  - President Alonzo Ames Miner, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02224; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; College presidents; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Miner, Alonzo Ames
  - Professor A.A. Keen, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02225; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Keen, A.A.
  - Thomas A. Goddard, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02226; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Benefactors; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Goddard, Thomas A.
  - Professor Benjamin G. Brown, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02227; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Brown, Benjamin G.; Dept. of Mathematics
  - Professor William Leslie Hooper, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02228; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; College presidents; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Hooper, William Leslie; Dept. of Physics; Dept. of Mathematics; College of Engineering
  - Professor William L. Hooper, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02229; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Dr. Edwin C. Bolles, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02230; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Bolles, Edwin Courtlandt; Dept. of English; Dept. of History
  - Professor C.M. Harmon, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02231; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Harmon, C.M.
  - Professor Amos E. Dolbear, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02232; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Dolbear, Amos Emerson; Dept. of Physics
  - Dr. Charles H. Leonard, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02233; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; College administrators; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Leonard, Charles H.; Divinity School
  - Professor William G. Tousey, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02234; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Tousey, William C.
  - Professor Frank W. Durkee, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02235; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Durkee, Frank W.; Dept. of Chemistry
  - Professor J. Sterling Kingsley, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02236; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Kingsley, J. Sterling
  - Sylvanus Packard, 1866; MS054.003.DO.02237; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Benefactors; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Packard, Sylvanus; Board of Trustees
  - President Capen reading in the library, 1870; MS054.003.DO.02239; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Faculty; College presidents; Libraries; People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Capen, Elmer Hewitt; Library
  - Hosea Ballou II, 1860; MS054.003.DO.02240; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Faculty; College presidents; People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Ballou, Hosea, 2d; Office of the President
  - Professor A. A. Keen, 1860; MS054.003.DO.02241; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Faculty; People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Keen, A.A.
  - Hodgdon Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02242; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts Buildings"
    Buildings; Dormitories; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Jackson College; Coll. of Liberal Arts & Jackson College
  - Ballou Hall, 1860; MS054.003.DO.02243; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Academic; Administrative; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; People; copy negative
  - Horse and buggy outside of Ballou Hall, 1871; MS054.003.DO.02244; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Ballou Hall, 1875; MS054.003.DO.02245; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Academic; Administrative; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Ballou Hall, 1875; MS054.003.DO.02246; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Engraving of Ballou Hall, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02247; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Back of Ballou Hall, 1879; MS054.003.DO.02248; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Administrative; Academic; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Ballou Hall with newly planted trees, 1860; MS054.003.DO.02249; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - West Hall, 1871; MS054.003.DO.02250; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - West Hall, 1871; MS054.003.DO.02251; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - West Hall, 1872; MS054.003.DO.02252; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Packard Hall, 1875; MS054.003.DO.02253; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Packard Hall, 1875; MS054.003.DO.02254; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Three unidentified men standing in front of Packard Hall and Barn, 1858; MS054.003.DO.02255; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; People; Dormitories; Academic; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Students lounging in front of East Hall, 1871; MS054.003.DO.02256; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; People; Students; Dormitories; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - East Hall dining room, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02257; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Food service; Dormitories; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Students in front of East Hall, 1874; MS054.003.DO.02258; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; People; Students; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - East Hall, 1868; MS054.003.DO.02259; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Dormitories; People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - East Hall, 1876; MS054.003.DO.02260; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Construction of Hodgdon Hall, 1954; MS054.003.DO.02261; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Hodgdon Hall, 1960; MS054.003.DO.02262; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Dearborn Gate in spring, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02263; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts Films, Vest Pocket Camera"
    Gates; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Dearborn Gate in fall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02264; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - East Hall, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02265; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - East Hall, 1940; MS054.003.DO.02266; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Barnum Hall, 1894; MS054.003.DO.02267; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Academic; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Barnum Hall, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02268; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Barnum Hall, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02269; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts Films, Vest Pocket Cameral"
  - West Hall, MS054.003.DO.02270; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Alumni Day, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02271; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Events; Alumni Day; Alumni and alumnae; People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Tufts theater, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02272; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Theater; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - AMRAD headquarters in North Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02273; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Radio Stations; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; AMRAD
  - Talbot Avenue at winter, MS054.003.DO.02274; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Eaton Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02275; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Libraries; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Tufts railroad station, MS054.003.DO.02276; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Goddard Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02277; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Flags flying during Class Day, MS054.003.DO.02278; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Views; Events; Class Day; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of campus, MS054.003.DO.02279; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - 13 Talbot Avenue, MS054.003.DO.02280; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - 72 Professors Row, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02281; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Boston Avenue in winter, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02282; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Square in front of Curtis Hall, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02283; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Administrative; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Looking north from East Hall, MS054.003.DO.02284; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - The old chemistry lab on Boston Avenue, 1930; MS054.003.DO.02285; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Laboratories; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Powder House, MS054.003.DO.02286; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Monuments; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of hill behind East Hall, 1930; MS054.003.DO.02287; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Views; Buildings; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of train from railroad bridge, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02288; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of college from Powder House, 1955; MS054.003.DO.02289; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Boston Avenue, MS054.003.DO.02290; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts Films, Vest Pocket Camera".
  - Dearborn Gate, MS054.003.DO.02291; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of Capen Street, MS054.003.DO.02292; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Pumphouse on the Rez, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02293; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Reservoirs; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of Professors Row, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02294; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Capen Street, 1900; MS054.003.DO.02295; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Children at the Bubbler, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02296; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    The Bubbler; People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View east from Robinson Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02297; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View north from Ballou Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02298; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Walkway behind Barnum Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02299; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    box: "Tufts Films, Vest Pocket Chairman"
  - View of west side of Packard Hall with the front of East Hall in the background, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02300; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Professors Row, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02301; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Robinson Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02302; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Robinson Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02303; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Packard Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02304; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Curtis Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02305; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Miner and Paige Halls, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02306; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Goddard Chapel, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02307; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Robinson Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02308; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Howe Memorial Laboratory, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02309; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Class Day activities, 1950; MS054.003.DO.02310; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Events; Class Day; People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Class Day Parade, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02311; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Police officers marching in Class Day Parade, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02312; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - People mingling during Class Day, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02313; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Listening to speeches during Class Day, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02314; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Class Day, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02315; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Events; Class Day; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Unidentified men in costume for Class Day activities, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02316; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Unidentified man in costume for Class Day activities, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02317; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Class Day time capsule, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02318; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Unidentified man in costume at Class Day activities, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02319; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Road toward Paige Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02320; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - The Schneider's home, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02321; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Old North Road, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02322; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Path leading behind Barnum Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02323; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Curtis Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02324; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Buildings; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - View of Professors Row, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02325; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Bromfield Pearson Building, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02326; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - College Avenue, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02327; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Goddard Chapel, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02328; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Miner Hall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02329; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Mr. C. Fall, 1910; MS054.003.DO.02330; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Hall, C.
  - Melville S. Munro with his camera, 1915; MS054.003.DO.02331; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Munro, Melville S.
  - Man identified only as Conner, 1915; MS054.003.DO.02332; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Poet John C. Ransom, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02333; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Ransom, John C.
  - Two women identified only as "Wright" and "Langdell,", 1910; MS054.003.DO.02334; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - People gathered in front of Ballou Hall, 1915; MS054.003.DO.02335; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Buildings; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Fred D. Lambert, Professor of Biology, 1915; MS054.003.DO.02336; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Lambert, Fred D.
  - Professor Leo Lewis, 1915; MS054.003.DO.02337; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Lewis, Leo R.
  - Professor Frank W. Durkee, 1920; MS054.003.DO.02338; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Faculty; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Durkee, Frank W.
  - Melville S. Munro standing beside a window pane, 1915; MS054.003.DO.02339; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Melville S. Munro with camera, 1915; MS054.003.DO.02340; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Man identified as P. Cobb walking along the road, 1915; MS054.003.DO.02341; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Cobb, P.
  - Man identified as Patrick Burns, 1915; MS054.003.DO.02342; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    People; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative; Burns, Patrick
  - Physics lab in Ballou Hall, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02343; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Laboratories; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Room in East Hall, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02344; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Rooms; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; copy negative
  - Room in West Hall, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02345; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Rooms; Edwin B. Rollins, papers; Interior views; People; copy negative
  - Looking accross recreation field toward campus, 1883; MS054.003.DO.02346; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Cows grazing on site of "The Oval,", 1890; MS054.003.DO.02347; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
    Views; copy negative
  - Packard Hall, 1876; MS054.003.DO.02348; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View southeast from Ballou Hall, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02349; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - College Avenue with The Hill in the background, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02350; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - West end of Professors Row from the Rez, 1890; MS054.003.DO.02351; Unknown; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View south from Ballou Hall, 1876; MS054.003.DO.02352; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Medford hillside from the Rez, 1879; MS054.003.DO.02353; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View eastward from the Rez, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02354; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - The Rez from Ballou Hall, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02355; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - Looking south from Ballou Hall, 1880; MS054.003.DO.02356; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of Medford hillside from the Rez, 1879; MS054.003.DO.02357; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View north from Ballou Hall, 1874; MS054.003.DO.02358; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View of West Medford from the Rez, 1875; MS054.003.DO.02359; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View southwest from Ballou Hall, 1877; MS054.003.DO.02360; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)
  - View southeast from Ballou Hall, 1886; MS054.003.DO.02361; Rollins, Edwin B. (Box Shared 117)